<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-12-13T15:27:51+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Janice Note</title><subtitle>This page will be making you find hype places as well as the brand in Korea easier and give some information about them.</subtitle><author><name>Minji Janice Cho</name><email>minjicho318@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">Cafe Afternoon Hong Kong</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/janice-note-cafe-afternoonhongkong/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cafe Afternoon Hong Kong" /><published>2019-12-13T11:50:00+09:00</published><updated>2019-12-13T11:50:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/afternoonhongkong</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/janice-note-cafe-afternoonhongkong/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/AfternoonHongKong-img.png&quot; alt=&quot;AfternoonHongKong&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;hey-i-am-in-hong-kong&quot;&gt;Hey, I am in Hong Kong!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a coffee lover or a milk tea geek, here is a fantastic place for you. This cafe I found a couple of days ago, which was looking extraordinary. Besides, this cafe is a rising place recently at sungshin university in seoul. When I saw it at first, I thought that it must be interiors like a characteristic night light atmosphere, cos the sign had a neon sign which was green colored as like hong kong’s town at night. However, this cafe was against my expectations when I entered the place. The wall inside has covered with bath tiles and somehow those tiles suggested an old fashioned bath of korea(even when I followed up upstairs with the banister, it made me felt more like i’m in a bathroom!). But when I looked at the 2nd floor, i changed my mind completely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/img_01.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2ndfloor&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interior was cozy rather than I thought. I felt like I was in the moment of the movie called chungking express. Moreover, the stand light furniture was on point with the tile interior as well as the well-designed broken wall. It led me into the mood kind of a little house in hong kong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/img_03.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;milktea&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;do-you-want-some-cup-of-tea&quot;&gt;Do you want some cup of tea?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you want a delight relish drink instead of coffee?  Or if you are the person who has a difficult to choose every moment or suffer from caffeine-related disorders? Then you have got an answer to take milk tea in korea. FYI, most of the milk tea in korea has normally a good quality of taste. and for sure, I would have to say milk tea is probably the best choice in this cafe as well. At this moment, i think you have a question about why I recommend this common tea for now? Of course, you can drink tea everywhere even if not in this cafe. But I want to say why I suggest you this milk tea is exceptional in every particular. Honestly, I don’t have a penchant for strong taste when it comes to tea things. In my case, if the tea has a strong flavor, it amplifies the bitter taste even more. In this respect, it is perfect for me and someone like me. This tea is so mild and light, but the flavor had vividly lingered in my mouth. Not for wild but so luscious. Even though it looks so simple, trust me, the taste might lead you gently into the heaven of tea!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/img_04.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bread&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, BTW, i just wanted you to know that the pineapple buns have been coming out at noon. Back then, I had no idea about the bread has been making in this cafe and even the time that they put out! So please make sure if you want to try fresh bread, you need to visit this place at the right hour as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you visit the place after see my blog later, please tell us in the comments below about your idea of how the bread was or what else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Address : 188-15 Heukseok-dong, Dongjak-gu, Seoul&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Hour : 10:00 - 22:00 (Mon-Sun)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Phone : 02-6398-6787&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Janice Cho</name></author><category term="cafe" /><category term="seoul" /><category term="coffee" /><category term="lifestyle" /><category term="Korea" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22feature%22=%3E%22AfternoonHongKong-img.png%22%7D" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22feature%22=%3E%22AfternoonHongKong-img.png%22%7D" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">About Janice Note</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/janice-note-about/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="About Janice Note" /><published>2019-12-12T15:35:00+09:00</published><updated>2019-12-12T15:35:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/about</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/janice-note-about/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;welcome&quot;&gt;Welcome!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/01/intro-img-1200x628px.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;ABOUT&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;to-all-the-people-who-have-adored-korea&quot;&gt;“To all the people who have adored Korea”&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi, welcome to Janice Note! I’m so glad you stopped by!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this blog will be able to help you to find a good place or a brand that you interest in Korea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working in the fashion industry as a designer, I’ve been getting inspiration from other places especially cafe as well as Korea fashion brands. Luckily, I could have learned and got motivation from not only artistic places but Korea brands. For this reason, I hope you will have a delightful memory in Korea through a story sharing about the place I have been to as a Korean in Seoul (sometimes giving information about Korean regions).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;you-cant-go-wrong-with-janice-note&quot;&gt;You can’t go wrong with Janice Note!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m an enthusiast of coffee as well as fashion. I’ve got numerous things to share the place where I’ve been visiting. Also, I can’t wait to inform you about a fashion brand which is rising stars in Korea. Let’s have fun with me in Korea and share a bunch of stories with other people who want to join us.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Janice Cho</name></author><category term="cafe" /><category term="fashion" /><category term="coffee" /><category term="lifestyle" /><category term="Korea" /><summary type="html">Welcome!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22feature%22=%3E%22thumb-main.jpg%22%7D" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22feature%22=%3E%22thumb-main.jpg%22%7D" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>